

Dawid Kaźmierczak

In my opinion IT industry is growing increasingly important in many organizations, and that will surely continue as technology continues to grow and increase. It is an exciting time for me to become a part of this business. Working in IT field will provide me with the sense of permanent development, therefore I would like to work with specialist to gain complex professional knowledge and to improve my skills.

Contact

Phone: +48 725 508 582

E-mail: dawkaz66@gmail.com Address: Kniaziewicza 21/21.

50-455 Wrocław

Skills

- Ability to make a decision under stress
- Good organizational skills
- Ability To Adapt To New Tech
- Analytical thinking
- Good communication skills
- Excellent planning and organisation skills
- Creative thinking and problem solving skills
- Ability to work both individually and in a team
- Knowledge of Linux and Bash scripting
- · Good knowledge of MS Office
- Basic knowledge of C++
- · Job Training certificate of ADR

Education

08/2018 - 05/2019 Software Development Academy

Java course:

08/2018 - 03/2019

- Java
- Version Control System GIT
- Java Virtual Maschine
- TDD jUnit
- Software Design Pattern
- MySQL, PostgreeSQL
- JDBC
- Hibernate framework
- HTTP
- REST APIs & basics of TCP/IP
- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- JavaEE (JSP, Java Servlety) 03/2019 - 04/2019
- Spring framework
- Agile (SCRUM)



2012 - 2016

School of Jazz and Stage Music

Saxophone class and piano

2011 - 2014
High School in Oleśnica

Math and physics profile

WORK EXPERIENCE

VGL Road



Road Freight Forwarder

03/2018 - present

- Handling customer service and operations for a variety of export and import shipments
- Overseeing each job from time of quotation to Invoicing
- Quoting customers / finding solutions for moving cargo both domestically and internationally
- Building, maintaining and developing good relationships with new and existing clients
- Achieving monthly profit targets
- Actively participating in implementing new procedures
- Onboarding new employees

Zinnar

Forwarder

11/2017 - 02/2018

- · Searching for international loads
- Knowing of transport law and related regulations to ensuring compliance of contract terms
- Maintaining and developing contact with foreign and local clients
- · Acquiring new business clients
- Issuing shipping documents and invoices

"La Vela" restaurant Chef



07-09/2017 (summer work)

- Prepering dishes
- · Taking care of supply and cleanness of working space
- · Coordinating serving of meals

Leo Trans



International driver

10/2016 - 03/2017

- · Delivering of both international and local loads
- Protecting of transported cargo
- Directly contacting with an international and domestic client
- Issuing shipping documents in accordance with the provisions of CMR convention

Camp Timanous

Campower - Kitchen Staff

06-09/2016 work and travel

- Organizing dining room
- Preparing dishes
- Taking care of supply
- · Working with international team

Kindelbruck Obstbau



06-08/2013 - 2015 summer work

- · Harvesting fruits
- · Working with german speaking foreman.

Hobbys

- Investing in financial markets
 - -Forex market
 - -CFD
 - -Index
- Economy
- . 17
- New technologies
- Athletic
- Windsurfing
- Snowboarding
- Traveling
- Craft

LANGUAGES

- Polish native
- English B2
- German A2
- Spanish basics, learn in progress